fairmark.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Fairmark.com Fairmark.com

As of May 31, 2012

Fairmark.com is a free consumer portal for information about taxes and investing. This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to information practices related to this website. Although this website contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those or any other sites. If you follow a link to another website you should read their privacy policy.

**Personal Information Collected on this Website**  
No personally identifiable information is collected on this website from consumers that browse the website for information.

Personally identifiable information collected on this website is gathered on pages where you register to receive our newsletter or post messages in the Fairmark Forum. We collect this information so that we can verify your registration and send the newsletter.

We record the IP address used when posting messages to the Fairmark Forum. This information is recorded for the sole purpose of identifying IP addresses that must be blocked to prevent spam postings.

Fairmark Press Inc. (“Fairmark”) is the sole owner of all information collected on this site. Fairmark will not rent, sell or share any personally-identifiable information about you with third parties for any reason except as required by law.

We do not send promotional emails or make information available to others for that purpose. Some promotional material may appear in our email newsletter. Our email newsletter is sent only to persons who request it (and confirm their request), and includes a link to cancel the subscription.

We do not merge any of the personally identifiable information collected via our registration forms with other anonymous data collected on our website.

**Anonymous Information Collected on this Website**  
We record anonymous data such as traffic logs, number of visits or clicks on a given page, pages viewed or links to our site. We use IP addresses and cookies for gathering website statistics.

We aggregate this anonymous data as part of managing, maintaining and reporting on use of our website. We may share this anonymous data with third parties.

None of this anonymous data is linked to personally identifiable information and we make no attempt to link IP addresses to the individuals who visit this site except as described above for those who post to the Fairmark Forum.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/).

**Cookies**  
We use cookies on this website.

Cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of your online patterns and preferences, as well as identify you as a return visitor. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible. No personally identifiable information is collected by or linked to any of the cookies delivered on our site.

You have the ability to manage the use of cookies on your computer using controls in your web-browser. To learn more about how to manage cookies, visit [All About Cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated.

**Questions?**  
Please [contact us](http://fairmark.com/fairmark/contact.htm) with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.
